export  const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "what is 1+3?",
        optionA: "2",
        optionB: "4",
        optionC:"1",
        optionD: "5",
        answer: "optionB",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 2-1?",
        optionA: "1",
        optionB: "0",
        optionC:"3",
        optionD: "5",
        answer: "optionA",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 5*3?",
        optionA: "5",
        optionB: "0",
        optionC:"3",
        optionD: "15",
        answer: "optionD",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 6/2?",
        optionA: "5",
        optionB: "3",
        optionC:"6",
        optionD:"2",
        answer:"optionB",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 2+5?",
        optionA: "5",
        optionB: "3",
        optionC:"6",
        optionD: "7",
        answer:"optionD",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 6-5?",
        optionA: "5",
        optionB: "1",
        optionC:"6",
        optionD: "7",
        answer: "optionB",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 2*1?",
        optionA: "2",
        optionB: "1",
        optionC:"6",
        optionD: "7",
        answer: "optionA",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 8/4?",
        optionA: "8",
        optionB: "4",
        optionC:"2",
        optionD: "6",
        answer: "optionA",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 5+9?",
        optionA: "12",
        optionB: "10",
        optionC:"14",
        optionD: "13",
        answer: "optionD",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 9-8?",
        optionA: "0",
        optionB: "7",
        optionC:"1",
        optionD: "2",
        answer: "optionC",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 3*2?",
        optionA: "3",
        optionB: "6",
        optionC:"1",
        optionD: "2",
        answer: "optionB",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 9/3?",
        optionA: "3",
        optionB: "6",
        optionC:"9",
        optionD: "2",
        answer: "optionA"
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 5+3?",
        optionA: "6",
        optionB: "8",
        optionC:"9",
        optionD: "2",
        answer: "optionB",
    },
    {
        prompt: "what is 8-5?",
        optionA: "6",
        optionB: "2",
        optionC:"1",
        optionD: "3",
        answer: "optionD",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 8*2?",
        optionA: "16",
        optionB: "4",
        optionC:"32",
        optionD: "12",
        answer: "optionA",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 2/2?",
        optionA: "0",
        optionB: "1",
        optionC:"2",
        optionD: "none",
        answer: "optionB",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 0+0?",
        optionA: "0",
        optionB: "1",
        optionC:"2",
        optionD: "none",
        answer: "optionA",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 0-0?",
        optionA: "0",
        optionB: "1",
        optionC:"2",
        optionD: "none",
        answer: "optionA",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 0*0?",
        optionA: "0",
        optionB: "1",
        optionC:"2",
        optionD: "none",
        answer: "optionA",
    },

    {
        prompt: "what is 0/0?",
        optionA: "0",
        optionB: "1",
        optionC:"2",
        optionD: "none",
        answer: "optionA",
    },
];